Hot sauce deeply dip that eh
Hot sauce sedalam mungkin dip that eh
Hot sauce 深く dip that eh
Hot sauce profundo dip that eh
Hot sauce ล้ำลึก dip that eh
Hot sauce 深深地 dip that eh
Hot sauce sâu hơn dip that eh
You follow me and twist that eh
Mengikutiku, kau twist that eh
僕を真似して君は twist that eh
Me sigues twist that eh
เธอตามฉันมา twist that eh
跟我来 你twist that eh
Làm theo anh này twist that eh
Hot sauce when it burns ooh
Hot sauce saat membakar ooh
Hot sauce 燃え上がる時 ooh
Hot sauce cuando quema ooh
Hot sauce แสนเผ็ดร้อน ooh
Hot sauce 燃烧时 ooh
Hot sauce khi bùng cháy ooh
Pick as you like ma dish
Pilih sesuai selera ma dish
口に合うもの選んで ma dish
A tu paladar elige ma dish
เลือกตามรสนิยม ma dish
随意挑选 ma dish
Chọn món hợp khẩu vị của em ma dish
what are you curious about
Apa yang membuatmu penasaran
君は何が知りたいの
Qué es lo que quieres saber
เธอสงสัยอะไร
你好奇什么
Em tò mò điều gì thế
I'm your personal chef
Aku hanya chef milikmu seorang
僕は君だけの chef
Yo soy tu exclusivo chef
ฉันเป็นของเธอ chef
我是你的专属chef
Chàng đầu bếp duy nhất của em là anh đây chef
This plate is for you
Ini plate untukmu
これは君のための plate
Esto es para ti plate
นี่สำหรับเธอ plate
这是为你准备的plate
Món này là dành cho em plate
yeah I'll let you taste it
yeah akan kutunjukkan rasanya
yeah 僕が味わせてあげるよ
yeah te mostraré cómo sabe
yeah ฉันจะแสดงให้เธอได้ลองชิม
yeah 我让你尝尝味道
yeah Để anh cho em nếm hương vị này
We have enough time now
Kita punya cukup waktu
時間は十分だ　今僕ら
Tiempo tenemos de sobra ahora
เวลาในตอนนี้ของเราเพียงพอแล้ว
时间很充足 现在我们
Chúng ta có đủ thời gian mà
Don't look around just taste it
Tak perlu melirikku, cukup taste it
周りの目も気にするな　ただ taste it
No te percates solamente taste it
ไม่ต้องกังวลอะไร แค่ taste it
不要察言观色 就这样 taste it
Đừng nhìn trước ngó sau nữa, hãy taste it
My secret is the unusual spicy
Rahasia resepku ada pada rasa spicy yang berbeda
僕の秘伝は風変わりな spicy
Mi secreto es un diferente spicy
วิธีของฉันช่างแสนพิเศษ spicy
我的秘诀是与众不同的spicy
Bí thuật của anh chính là vị cay độc lạ spicy
Just passing by it makes you crazy
Sedikit saja kau cicipi akan membuat kehilangan akal
かすかに触れるだけで無我夢中さ
Un sutil roce te agita
แค่เฉียดไปก็ทำให้มึนงงได้
轻轻掠过就会魂牵梦绕
Chỉ thoáng qua thôi cũng khiến em cuồng điên
It's easy to get sick of the sugarcoated taste
Memang gampang merasa bosan dengan rasa manis gula
砂糖が塗られた味はすぐ飽きやすい
Untado en azúcar te empalaga fácil
รสชาติแห่งความหวานมันน่าเบื่อ
抹了糖的味道容易让人发腻
Vị ngọt của đường thì rất dễ chán
You felt my heated feelin’ just now
Kau bisa merasakan feelin’ panas dariku sekarang
熱い僕の feelin’ 今感じた　君は
Caliente mi feelin’ lo has sentido ahora
เธอสัมผัสได้ถึงความเร่าร้อน feelin’ ของฉัน
我火热的feelin’你现在感受到了吧
Em đã thấy feelin' bùng cháy của anh chưa
The clearly visible heat between you and me keeps getting hotter
Hawa panas yang jelas tumbuh di antara kau dan aku
君と僕の間　鮮やかに見えた大きくなっていく熱気
Entre tú y yo claramente se ve el ardor que se agranda
ความร้อนแรงที่ทวีขึ้นอย่างชัดเจนระหว่างเธอกับฉัน
你和我之间渐增的热气清晰可见
Mối quan hệ của anh và em ngày càng cuồng nhiệt
I wake up the five senses, I wake up your feelings, it feels like exploding ma skill
Aku membangunkan kelima inderamu, hatimu yang akan meledak bagai ma skill
僕は五感を呼び覚ます 君の心を呼び覚ます　爆発しそうな ma skill
Yo despierto los sentidos Despierto tu alma es para explotar ma skill
ฉันปลุกประสาทสัมผัสทั้งห้า ปลุกหัวใจของเธอ ราวกับจะระเบิด ma skill
唤醒五感 唤醒你的心 放佛要爆炸的ma skill
Đánh thức năm giác quan trong anh, đánh thức cảm xúc trong em, cảm giác như muốn nổ tung ma skill
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
Hot sauce deeply dip that eh
Hot sauce sedalam mungkin dip that eh
Hot sauce 深く dip that eh
Hot sauce profundo dip that eh
Hot sauce ล้ำลึก dip that eh
Hot sauce 深深地 dip that eh
Hot sauce sâu hơn dip that eh
You follow me and twist that eh
Mengikutiku, kau twist that eh
僕を真似して君は twist that eh
Me sigues twist that eh
เธอตามฉันมา twist that eh
跟我来 你twist that eh
Làm theo anh này twist that eh
Hot sauce when it burns ooh
Hot sauce saat membakar ooh
Hot sauce 燃え上がる時 ooh
Hot sauce cuando quema ooh
Hot sauce แสนเผ็ดร้อน ooh
Hot sauce 燃烧时 ooh
Hot sauce khi bùng cháy ooh
Pick as you like ma dish
Pilih sesuai selera ma dish
口に合うもの選んで ma dish
A tu paladar elige ma dish
เลือกตามรสนิยม ma dish
随意挑选 ma dish
Chọn món hợp khẩu vị của em ma dish
Don't let your guard down at all uh
Jangan lengah sama sekali uh
まったく油断するな uh
Ni se te ocurra descuidarte uh
อย่าเผลอตัวเกินไป uh
千万不要掉以轻心 uh
Đừng cảnh giác làm gì uh
It'll be watertight
Karena tak akan ada celah
抜け目はないはずだから
Grietas no hay
เพราะจะไม่มีช่องว่างใด
因为无懈可击
Chẳng có sai sót nào đâu
Yeah my stimulating senses, can you
Yeah kau adalah inspirasi rasaku
Yeah 君は刺激的な僕の感覚
Yeah tú eres mi sensación provocante
Yeah เธอ กระตุ้นความรู้สึกของฉัน
Yeah 我这份充满刺激的感觉
Yeah em kích thích các giác quan trong anh
ooh handle it nope
ooh apa kau mampu mengatasinya nope
ooh 手に負えるかな nope
ooh podrás manejarte nope
ooh จะรับมือฉันไหวไหม nope
ooh 你能承受的了吗 nope
ooh, vậy có được không, giải quyết đi nope
Yeah yeah there's no way you can withstand it na
Yeah yeah kau tak perlu bertahan na
Yeah yeah 耐えられるはずないじゃないか na
Yeah yeah No podrás aguantarlo na
Yeah yeah ไม่มีเหตุผลที่ต้องทน na
Yeah yeah 无法坚持啊 na
yeah yeah không thể chịu đựng được na
Relax more and bon appétit now that’s right
Cobalah untuk santai, kau bon appétit now that’s right
緊張をもっとほぐして君は bon appétit now that’s right
Relájate más y tú bon appétit now that’s right
ทำใจให้ผ่อนคลายสิ bon appétit now that’s right
更加放松 你bon appétit now that’s right
em đã bớt căng thẳng hơn bon appétit now that’s right
You can't control it, you keep falling for the taste
Tak bisa kukendalikan, rasa yang terus menarikku
コントロールできずハマっていく味
No puedes controlarlo este sabor que atrapa
รับมือไม่ไหว มัวเมาไปกับรสชาตินี้
无法控制 总是让人深陷的味道
không thể kiểm soát, càng lúc càng đắm chìm vào hương vị đó
cuz you can’t stop until the end I get ya
cuz you can’t stop aku hingga akhir get ya
cuz you can’t stop 僕は最後まで get ya
cuz you can’t stop Voy hasta el final get ya
cuz you can’t stop ฉันจะไปให้ถึงที่สุด get ya
cuz you can’t stop 我到最后 get ya
cuz you can't stop đến tận cùng get ya
You'll look for it every day (and every night)
Pasti akan terus mencari every day (and every night)
探すことになるはずさ every day (and every night)
Lo buscarás every day (and every night)
แล้วเธอจะต้องการ every day (and every night)
会不断寻求 every day (and every night)
Hương vị anh luôn kiếm tìm every day (and every night)
You're addicted already
Kau sudah ketagihan
病みつきになる　すでに君は
Adicto ya estás
เพราะเธอติดใจเสียแล้ว
你已经中毒了
Em nghiện mất rồi
Stir up your feelings more (without leaving anything now)
Lebih mengaduk hatimu (tanpa tersisa)
君の心をもっと混ぜておく（もうすっかり）
Más mezcla tu corazón (Ahora sin dejar nada)
ผสมใจของเธออีก (ไม่มียั้ง)
把你的心搅在一起 (现在起毫无保留)
Khuấy động cảm xúc của em thêm nữa (Chẳng giữ lại gì)
You'll keep wanting it
Membuatmu terus menginginkannya
ずっと欲しくなる
Te hace querer más
เธอจะต้องการอยู่ตลอด
会一直渴望
Không ngừng khao khát
You feel dizzy, your hands and feet are already drawn to me
Pikiranmu dan kedua tangan dan kakimu telah tertarik padaku
くらくらする頭　君の両手足が導かれる　すでに僕に
Mareada la cabeza tus dos manos y pies ya cautivados
หัวที่มึนงง มือและเท้าเธอถูกดึงดูดมาหาฉัน
乱哄哄的脑袋已牵动你的手脚走向我
Đầu óc quay cuồng, cả tay chân em đã bị cuốn về phía anh
Every stimulating moment is so intense what we gon’ eat
Tiap suasana yang mengintimidasi jadi lebih intens what we gon’ eat
もっと刺激的な一瞬一瞬が強烈だ what we gon’ eat
Intensos momentos un poco más excitantes what we gon’ eat
ทุกทีที่กระตุ้น มันจะรุนแรงขึ้น what we gon’ eat
更加刺激的每个瞬间强烈无比 what we gon’ eat
Những khoảnh khắc kích thích càng dữ dội hơn what we gon’ eat
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
(I’m the one what you want what you want what you want ah ya)
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
(I’m the one what you want what you want what you want ah ya)
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
Hot sauce deeply dip that eh
Hot sauce sedalam mungkin dip that eh
Hot sauce 深く dip that eh
Hot sauce profundo dip that eh
Hot sauce ล้ำลึก dip that eh
Hot sauce 深深地 dip that eh
Hot sauce sâu hơn dip that eh
You follow me and twist that eh
Mengikutiku, kau twist that eh
僕を真似して君は twist that eh
Me sigues twist that eh
เธอตามฉันมา twist that eh
跟我来 你twist that eh
Làm theo anh này twist that eh
Hot sauce when it burns ooh
Hot sauce saat membakar ooh
Hot sauce 燃え上がる時 ooh
Hot sauce cuando quema ooh
Hot sauce แสนเผ็ดร้อน ooh
Hot sauce 燃烧时 ooh
Hot sauce khi bùng cháy ooh
Pick as you like ma dish
Pilih sesuai selera ma dish
口に合うもの選んで ma dish
A tu paladar elige ma dish
เลือกตามรสนิยม ma dish
随意挑选 ma dish
Chọn món hợp khẩu vị của em ma dish
Your feelin’ swallowed you up
feelin’ yang menelanmu
君を飲み込んでしまった feelin’
Te ha tragado este feelin’
กลืนกินเธอ feelin’
吞噬你的 feelin’
Thứ cảm giác như muốn nuốt lấy em feelin'
This captivating attraction
Ketertarikan yang memikat ini
惹きつけたこんな魅力
Cautivado en esta atracción
ความดึงดูดเกินต้านทาน
这致命的吸引力
Một sức hút đầy mê hoặc
You can't separate it
Tak bisa dilepaskan
切り離せないだろ
No puedes separarte
ไม่อาจละสายตา
让人无法摆脱
Chẳng thể dứt ra được
When you fall for it more
Saat kau jatuh lebih dalam
さらに深くハマっていく時
Cuando más profundo te metes
เมื่อลุ่มหลงอย่างล้ำลึก
越陷越深的时候
Càng đắm chìm sâu hơn
You want it want it want it even more babe
Ingin ingin inginkan lebih babe
欲しがって　欲しがって　欲しがってみて　もっと babe
Deseo deseo lo deseas más babe
ต้องการอีกสิ ต้องการอีกสิ ต้องการอีกสิ มากกว่านี้ babe
想要 想要 更加想要 babe
Anh lại càng muốn thêm muốn thêm muốn thêm nữa babe
Ask for more as much as you want babe
Mintalah seberapapun terus dan terus babe
いくらでももっと欲しがって　欲しがって babe
Cuanto quieras deséalo más babe
หวังว่าจะได้มากกว่า มากกว่านี้ babe
不管多少都想要 babe
Bao nhiêu nữa cũng được babe
Enjoy the perfect taste lingering over the tip of your tongue
Nikmati rasa yang sempurna di ujung lidahmu
君の舌先の上でちらつく完璧な味を楽しんで
En la punta de tu lengua arde Disfruta este sabor perfecto
สนุกไปกับรสชาติที่สมบูรณ์แบบอันเลือนรางที่ปลายลิ้น
享受在你舌尖上跳动的完美味道
Thưởng thức hương vị hoàn hảo vương vấn trên đầu lưỡi em
You want it babe
(I’m the one what you want what you want what you want ah ya)
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
(I’m the one what you want what you want what you want ah ya)
Pick ma dish
Pilih ma dish
選んで ma dish
Escoge ma dish
เลือกสิ เลือก ma dish
选吧 ma dish
Chọn đi ma dish
Hot sauce deeply dip that eh
Hot sauce sedalam mungkin dip that eh
Hot sauce 深く dip that eh
Hot sauce profundo dip that eh
Hot sauce ล้ำลึก dip that eh
Hot sauce 深深地 dip that eh
Hot sauce sâu hơn dip that eh
You follow me and twist that eh
Mengikutiku, kau twist that eh
僕を真似して君は twist that eh
Me sigues twist that eh
เธอตามฉันมา twist that eh
跟我来 你twist that eh
Làm theo anh này twist that eh
Hot sauce when it burns ooh
Hot sauce saat membakar ooh
Hot sauce 燃え上がる時 ooh
Hot sauce cuando quema ooh
Hot sauce แสนเผ็ดร้อน ooh
Hot sauce 燃烧时 ooh
Hot sauce khi bùng cháy ooh
Pick as you like ma dish
Pilih sesuai selera ma dish
口に合うもの選んで ma dish
A tu paladar elige ma dish
เลือกตามรสนิยม ma dish
随意挑选 ma dish
Chọn món hợp khẩu vị của em ma dish